strongvaultfree.com 2013-12-08

# Privacy_policy

The software you are about to download or have already downloaded contains the Strongvault Online Backup software ("Strongvault Software") brought to you by Strongvault Online Storage LLC and an advertising add-on (as further described below, the "LeadImpact Software") brought to you by Lead Impact Sub LLC. Your use of the Strongvault Software is governed exclusively by the Strongvault Terms of Use below and Strongvault Privacy Policy, and your use of the LeadImpact Software is governed exclusively by the LeadImpact End User License Agreement for Strongvault Users and the LeadImpact Privacy Policy for Strongvault Users. By downloading or using the Strongvault Software, you expressly acknowledge that you have read, understood, accept and agree to each of the terms and conditions set forth in the (i) Strongvault Terms of Use, (ii) Strongvault Privacy Policy, (iii) LeadImpact End User License Agreement for Strongvault Users and (iv) LeadImpact Privacy for Strongvault Users. 

#### PRIVACY POLICY

This website (and any and all sub-domains) (the "Site") and any and all online back-up services and software provided through the Site (collectively with the Site, the "Services") is owned and operated by Strongvault Online Storage LLC ("Strongvault"). For the purposes hereof, the users of the Site and Services are referred to as "you", "your" or "User" and Strongvault is referred to as the "Company", "we", "us" or "our".

The privacy of users that access our Services is very important to us, and accordingly, we have formulated the Privacy Policy (the "Policy" or "Privacy Policy") to inform you about how we intend to collect, use, disclose and protect your Personal Information (as defined below) that is received in connection with the Services. We seek to handle your Personal Information in a manner that complies fully with the privacy principles and requirements under all applicable United States federal and state privacy legislation and regulations. 

All Users will be subject to and bound by this Policy as well as the Terms of Use available at http://www.strongvaultfree.com/terms. By accessing, browsing and/or using the Services, you are accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use and you expressly acknowledge that you have read and understood the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use and that you agree and consent to the use of your Personal Information pursuant to the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth in the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, then please do not provide us with any information and do not access, browse or use the Services. 

#### General

You agree and warrant that any and all of your personal information provided to us is true and correct, including, but not limited to, your name, physical or electronic mailing address, phone number, fax number and other information requested (and you agree to update the same for the duration of this Policy). You understand that all personal information provided by you to us will be subject to the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by any applicable law, or if we, in our sole and absolute discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable or necessary to (1) comply with any applicable law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is affirmatively required by applicable law); or (2) protect or defend the rights or property of the Company or any third party. 

#### Personal Information

The Company, including its employees, agents, independent contractors and/or representatives, will collect personal information as discussed below ("Personal Information") in a number of circumstances in the course of providing Services. 

We do or may in the future collect Personal Information in connection with the Services, such as (without limitation) when users register for Services, use the Site, provide credit card or payment information, request publications or other information from us, sign up for newsletters, participate in user posting areas (such as bulletin boards, discussion forums, and surveys) and obtain or provide user access credentials. 

Personal Information we will or may collect from users includes (without limitation): (a) names, physical and email addresses, telephone and facsimile numbers, internet protocol (IP) addresses and other business and/or residential contact information; (b) information or comments provided on the Services or otherwise, including feedback and comments about you with respect to the Services; (c) information regarding your activity on the Site, including (without limitation) your browsing patterns, download activity and pages viewed; (d) credit card and payment information; and (e) such other information we may collect with consent or as permitted or required by law. 

We may use other technologies including, but not limited to, pixel tags, web beacons, and technologies that enable us to be aware of your operating systems, hardware configurations, software applications that may be installed on your computer, and pages you visited on the Site. These technologies are employed to allow us to improve our Services. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to personally identifiable information. 

#### Use of Personal Information

The Company generally uses Personal Information for the following purposes: (a) identification; (b) establishment and maintenance of our relationship with you, (c) to provide you with ongoing news, publications and information, to respond to your requests and inquiries, to fulfill your requests to register for Services, use the Site, provide credit card or payment information to us, request publications or other information from us, sign up for newsletters, participate in user posting areas (such as bulletin boards, discussion forums, and surveys) and obtain or provide user access credentials.; (d) marketing purposes, such as your Site activity, browsing and usage information and/or your demographic information that you may have voluntarily provided to us, in order to better tailor our marketing activities and to implement and maintain loyalty programs; (e) providing information to third-party administrators or other providers necessary to optimize the Services; (f) maintaining business records for reasonable periods, and generally managing and administering our business; (g) meeting legal, regulatory, insurance, security and processing requirements and court or administrative orders; and (h) otherwise with consent or as permitted or required by law. 

We may keep any and all of your Personal Information on hand for as long as permitted by law for any and all of the purposes described herein. 

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Personal Information may be disclosed to: (a) our employees, agents, representatives, advisors, affiliates and independent contractors, in connection with their performance of services for or on behalf of the Company; (b) service providers who help us with our business operations, sales and marketing, information technology or professional services; and (c) third parties who purchase leads from the Company ("Third Party Partner"). Personal Information may be used by the Company and disclosed to parties in connection with the contemplated or actual financing, securitization, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of the Company or our business or assets, including (without limitation) for the purposes of: permitting such parties to determine whether or not to proceed or continue with such transaction. In the event that all or part of the Company or our business or assets is sold, assigned or otherwise disposed of, Personal Information we have collected will be used and disclosed by such parties for substantially the same purposes as described in the Privacy Policy. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose your personal information: (a) as required under law or to meet legal, regulatory, insurance, audit, and security requirements, with your consent, or as permitted or required by law; (b) pursuant to a subpoena or other legal action; (c) where we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected situations involving potential threats to the property rights or physical safety of any person; or (d) in the event of a violation of our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use. The Company may also freely disclose your personal information to third party service providers under conditions of confidentiality in order to provide the Services. These third-party service providers may include (without limitation) auditors, hosting providers, Internet Service Providers, software providers, information technology service providers, server and data providers, and e-mail validation services. 

#### The Site

The Company operates and maintains the Site at www.strongvaultfree.com (and any and all sub-domains thereof). In general, you can visit the Site and view basic content while remaining anonymous by not providing any Personal Information; provided, however, we do collect your IP address and cookie information. 

Our Site may collect non-personally identifiable information that becomes available to us as a result of your visit to our Site. This information includes, for example, your IP address (a number automatically assigned to your computer when you visit the Site, and which is logged by our servers) your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"), your web browser, the type of operating system, the domain name of the website which links you to our Site and the pages you visited while you were using the Site. 

#### Cookies

We do use cookies on the Site. Cookies are small text files that your web browser leaves on your hard drive to recognize you as a repeat user of the Site, track your use of the Site and target marketing and advertising. This allows for personalization of certain aspects of your visit to our Site. Information gathered from cookies in this way is only used on an aggregate basis. Unless a visitor specifically provides their identity to us, e.g., by registering at our Site, providing information through an online form or sending us correspondence from the Site, we will not know who the individual visitors are. We may use cookies to store preferences; record session information; develop information about Site visitors' preferences and interests; record past activity at the Site in order to provide better information when you return to our Site; or customize web page content based on information you voluntarily provide. 

You can disable cookies using your Internet browser settings. Please consult your web browser's help function for information on how to disable cookies. Note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Site may not function properly. 

#### Security

We take reasonable steps to safeguard your Personal Information and endeavor to keep it secure using security measures that are appropriate for a company and website of our scope and size in our industry. Despite these precautions, the Company cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will not obtain access to Personal Information. 

#### Consent

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (for example, orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of Personal Information) or implied (for example, when you provide information necessary for a user access or access credentials that you have requested) or given in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your Personal Information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an "opt out" option provided, if any. Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, by providing us with Personal Information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information for the purposes identified or described in the Privacy Policy, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information at any time by contacting us as indicated below, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. Please note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your Personal Information then we may no longer be able to provide you with certain of our products or services. 

Each User is deemed to consent to receiving periodic email messages from the Company, unless the User has expressed a desire to unsubscribe and not receive such messages. The email messages may include, without limitation, information and advertisements from the Company and its partners. The Company will generally not share, sell or market the email addresses or other collected personal information of Users to third parties other than as set forth herein. The Company collects, utilizes and discloses your Personal Information with your consent, except as permitted or required by law. We may be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose Personal Information without your consent, for example to comply with a court order, to comply with local, federal or foreign regulations or a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency, or to collect a debt owed to us. Please bear in mind that the Company is based in the United States, and we do not necessarily attempt to comply with foreign (non-U.S.) privacy legislation. By consenting (in any manner described above) to our collection, usage and disclosure of your Personal Information, you acknowledge and understand that the Site may be viewed and hosted anywhere in the world, and furthermore, you agree that your Personal Information may be transferred across national boundaries. 

#### Access and Control of Your Personal Information

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction, so we offer several ways for you to update your Personal Information, change your preferences, or opt out of receiving future communications. 

1\. If you have an account at the Site or in connection with the Services, you may be able to log on and update or change your Personal Information or account information. Check the Site for further information. 

2\. You may unsubscribe to any of our online e-mail updates or newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message. You may unsubscribe to any communications from Third Party Partners by following the opt-out procedures contained in the e-mail or written communication sent by the applicable Third Party Partner. 

3\. You may also contact us at support@strongvaultfree.com or write to us at Strongvault Online Storage LLC, P.O. Box 12675, Newport Beach, CA 92658 for any inquiry or request regarding our privacy policy or the handling of your Personal Information. 

If you have opted out of receiving future e-mails from us, we will implement your opt-out request within 10 business days of receiving the opt-out request. If you have opted out of receiving future promotional materials by regular mail, we will implement your opt-out request within a commercially reasonable time. 

#### Links

The Services may contain links and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. The Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, products or services on such third-party sites. Third-party links and pointers are included solely for the convenience of Users, and do not constitute any endorsement or verification thereof by the Company. You expressly agree to assume sole responsibility for use and access of third party links and pointers. Please recognize that we do not control these third party websites and the Privacy Policy will not apply to any of these websites. You should consult the applicable privacy policy of each third party website before using such third party linked website, as your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy on such linked website. 

#### International Users

This Privacy Policy and all matters relating to Services are governed by the laws of the State of California in the United States. If you are accessing our Service from outside of the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. Your use of the Services indicates your consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities anywhere across the world and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of Personal Information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to customerservice@strongvaultfree.com and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, and provide us with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request. 

#### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

The Company is strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who use the Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information online from children under 13. We encourage all parents to talk to their kids about online safety and to monitor their children's use of the Internet. The Company does not attempt to, or knowingly ask for or, collect information from any person under the age of 13. We recommend that children ask a parent for permission before sending any Personal Information anywhere using the Internet. You must be over the age of 18 to use the Services. 

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Services and not to any information collected offline. 

#### Changes

The Company may, in its sole and absolute discretion, modify or change any or every aspect of the Policy at any time (for any reason or no reason), effective immediately upon posting such modifications or changes (or a revised version of this Policy incorporating such modifications or changes therein) on or through the Site. Please periodically consult the end of this Policy to determine when the Policy was last revised. You agree to periodically review this Policy to ensure that you are in compliance with any ongoing changes or modifications that are made to the Policy. Your continued use of the Services after any such modifications or changes are posted will constitute your complete and unequivocal acceptance of such any modifications or changes to the Policy. The Company reserves the right, but has no obligation whatsoever, to modify or change the Policy as it applies to any specific User, provided that any and all such special modifications must be in writing and signed by and between the Company and the applicable User. Any specialized modifications so made shall apply exclusively and only to the User that is a party to such written agreement. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions, thoughts our comments with respect to our Privacy Policy, please contact us by writing us at: support@strongvaultfree.com

Or you can contact us by mail at: 

Strongvault Online Storage LLC P.O. Box 12675 Newport Beach, CA 92658

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the posted Privacy Policy when you visit the Site to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. Your continued use of the Services means you accept the updated Privacy Policy. 

#### LeadImpact Privacy Policy for Strongvault Users

Lead Impact Sub LLC, its affiliates, licensors and licensees, ("LeadImpact" or "we"), are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to any web site that references this Privacy Policy and is provided by LeadImpact ("Web site"), and to those LeadImpact -owned software products ("Software) made available to you from a Web site. Please see below for important information on third party software products made available from the Web sites. This Privacy Policy also governs information that you provide to us or that we learn from you when you use our Web sites and Software (collectively "Products"). When we collect your information from our Products, we will tell you how we may collect, use, and, in some instances, share this information. What We Collect and Use 

#### Cookies. 

By accessing any Web site, LeadImpact may place cookies on your hard drive. LeadImpact uses cookies to enable you to sign in to certain services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Some cookies are used only to assist you with your session on a Web site - such cookies expire automatically after you terminate your session. LeadImpact also uses cookies to improve the sign-in experience on certain Web sites. For example, your user ID may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you terminate your session. This cookie allows your user ID to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. Finally, LeadImpact may place a cookie on your hard disk on behalf of a sponsor when an advertisement for that sponsor is shown, so that the sponsor can measure the effectiveness of that advertisement. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies can only be accessed or read by the domain that placed them. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use certain features of a Web site that depend on cookies. 

#### User-Provided Information. 

In order to utilize the services at some Web sites you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information ("PII"), such as account information (user name and password), credit card information (card type, account number, expiration date, and billing address), banking information (Swift/ABA routing number, account number, bank name and address), PayPal email, email address, IM user ID, name and company name, tax identification number, and home or work address and telephone number, as well as certain demographic information such as city, state, country and zip code. LeadImpact uses your PII to deliver the services you have requested and to communicate with you, including certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from LeadImpact. All such information is provided voluntarily by you. If you provide a friend's email address to LeadImpact for the "refer-a-friend" feature, we use that email address only for the purpose of sending your friend the email you requested. No PII is utilized by LeadImpact for the purpose of displaying advertisements or for profiling. LeadImpact does not sell, rent or lease PII to third parties. 

#### Credit Cards.

When credit card data is required for services, we protect your credit card information using industry standard SSL encryption whenever card data is transmitted to us and when sending your credit card information to our credit card processor. While in our possession, your credit card number is protected with asymmetric encryption to keep it secure. 

#### Software. 

In order to use Software, you may be asked to provide certain information. All such information is provided voluntarily by you. No such information is utilized by LeadImpact for the purpose of displaying advertisements or profiling. LeadImpact does not sell, rent or lease such information to third parties. Our Software product automatically collects information from you to enable the Software's services. By installing the Software, you authorize LeadImpact to periodically collect certain information, such as (1) keywords and portions of Web site addresses or complete URLs from the Web sites you visit and upload this information to our servers so that we may display targeted advertisements to you while you are connected to the Internet The Software does not collect, store, or use PII, and LeadImpact does not receive PII, as a result of your use of this Software. 

#### Third Party Software. 

Included with the Software may be third party software from a LeadImpact partner. Your registration for and use of any third party software is subject to that third party's privacy policy, if any. If you register for or use third party software, both LeadImpact and the third party software provider will receive any information collected by LeadImpact in conjunction with your registration, and only LeadImpact 's use of your information is subject to this Privacy Policy. To determine how a LeadImpact partner may use your registration information, or may otherwise independently be collecting other information through your use of third party software, please refer to the third party software provider's privacy policy. 

#### No Information from Minors. 

You must be at least 18 years of age to use the Products. 

#### IP Addresses. 

Your use of the Products will involve the transmission of your Internet protocol address ("IP Address") to LeadImpact 's servers. This IP Address is necessary for communication with you via the Internet and may be used and stored on our servers. We use IP Addresses to determine the general geographic locations of our users; we do not link IP addresses to identify you personally for marketing purposes. LeadImpact does not share non-PII (pseudonymous) information with third parties. 

#### Third Party Collection. 

The Software will display to you targeted web sites and/or advertisements that are hosted by third parties ("Third Party Hosted Advertisements"). These Third Party Hosted Advertisements may place cookies on your hard drive and use the cookies to tailor delivery of content to you by profiling your use of a web site or advertisements that you select. These Third Party Hosted Advertisements may collect information such as your IP address, your browser type and the date and time that the targeted Third Party Hosted Advertisement was served to you. To learn about how certain of these third parties collect and use information visit http://www.networkadvertising.org. 

#### Disclosure. 

LeadImpact may disclose your information as it believes is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation, or other governmental authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others. LeadImpact may also disclose your information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of LeadImpact 's stock or assets in LeadImpact 's line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization. 

#### Control of your Personal Information. 

LeadImpact offers you choices for the collection, use, and sharing of your personal information. You may choose not to receive marketing materials from LeadImpact, and you may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from LeadImpact by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. These communications choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain LeadImpact services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service. You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information, and can either do so through the applicable Web site or by writing to us using our Contact Us form. We will contact you within 30 days regarding your request. 

#### Linking to Other Sites. 

A link on a Web site or on a Third Party web site does not imply LeadImpact 's endorsement of such linked web site, advertiser, or product. We do not necessarily control the web sites to which we link and, in any event, assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Any information that you provide to linked web sites, or other third parties, is provided directly to such third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Therefore, you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any web sites you access from the Products, and any advertisers you respond to. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by LeadImpact. 

#### Changes and Updates. 

LeadImpact reserves the right to change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. LeadImpact will post those changes on the privacy page of each Web site so you can be aware of what information we collect and how we use it. Your use of the Products following the posting of any change to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any such changes. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy frequently to make sure that you understand how LeadImpact collects, uses, and discloses information. 

#### Contact Us. 

If you have any questions about Pinball's Lead Impact program, a Pinball Web site, or any Software or related services, you should first consult the Pinball Web site at http://www.leadimpact.com. If you have further questions or concerns, please contact us at http://www.leadimpact.com/about/contactus.aspx or write to LeadImpact Support, 3600 136th Place SE, Bellevue, WA 98006. 

#### Revision Date

This Agreement was last revised on June 17th, 2013
